Sushant Kunwar Chhetri

Contact

- Bardaghat-4,
 Nawalparasi
- 9847299660
- 🔽 sushantkch@gmail.com

Skills

- Data Management
- Teamwork
- Customer Services
- Effective Communication
- · Critical Thinking
- UI Design
- E-commerce with Prototypes
- HTML & CSS
- User Research Analysis
- User Experience Design

Language

- English
- Nepalese

Projects

https://www.figma.com/design/OnZAAtbKGxDEFDo14j85AL/Untitled?node-id=86-6715&t=miDRnpcxU4mc9X77-1

https://github.com/

SushantJungChhetri/Next-

WorkForce-Solution.git

Profile

Skilled content with solid academic preparation and extensive experience in intelligence and special operations seeks position in Barista with over 1.5 year experience and also work as a Data Entry Staff in company with over 6-8 months experience. Proven ability to assess and manage complex obstacles; viewed as a strong troubleshooter. Successful in intense and demanding environments, providing decisive team leadership and structure with a track record of motivating and developing soldiers.

Work Experience

Suruchi Suppliers

Data Entry Staff

04/2022 - 09/2023

Bardaghat-4, Nawalparasi

- · Entered data into the system with speed and accurately.
- Managed and updated client records, ensuring data integrity.
- · Assisted with file transfers and backups.
- Implemented artificial intelligence tools in our workflow.

R.B. Cafe & Restro

Barista

11/2020 - 01/2022

Bardaghat-9, Nawalparasi

- Took coffee, food, and other beverage orders and prepared them for
- · customers quickly and effectively.
- Maintained a clean and professional appearance and dining area for
- · guest satisfaction.
- Washed dishes and restocked the bar line for continued fast service capabilities.

Education

ISMT College

BSc IT (Hons) in Computer Engineering

2023 - Ongoing

Manimukunda College (+2)

Science Faculty

2020 pass out

New Life Secondary School (SEE)

2018 pass out